<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>STIR</title>
    <link>https://news.aus.edu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on STIR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 15:55:00 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://news.aus.edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Two minutes with... Dr. Ilias Visvikis, Director of AUS Executive Education</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 15:55:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news7/</guid>
      <description>What is special about AUS Executive Education?  We are able to offer our partners a unique combination of academic knowledge, combined with hands-on business experience and new learning technologies. Our experts have deep insight of the region, but have also worked in business and academia around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STIR February 2019</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/email/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 11:10:12 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/email/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About AUS</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:37:45 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news8/</guid>
      <description>American University of Sharjah (AUS) was founded in 1997 by His Highness Sheikh Dr. Sultan Bin Muhammad Al Qasimi, Member of the Supreme Council of the United Arab Emirates and Ruler of Sharjah. Sheikh Sultan articulated his vision of a distinctive institution against the backdrop of Islamic history and in the context of the aspirations and needs of contemporary society in the UAE and the Gulf region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Around campus: New psychology program on offer</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:37:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news6/</guid>
      <description>As demand increases across the Arab world for highly trained psychologists, AUS has launched a new program that will help fill the region’s skills gap in the expanding field of psychology. With the region continuing to experience rapid population growth and economic development, it is expected that there will be concurrent growth in psychology-related fields, in both the public and private sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the press: SBA students “leaders of the future”</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:37:34 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news5/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jörg Bley, Dean of the AUS School of Business Administration, has told Arabian Business: ““At SBA, we not only concentrate on giving our students an outstanding academic basis for their future career, but also focus on equipping them with the 21st century skills today’s top employers demand: team work, critical thinking, effective communication and inspirational leadership, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A word from our blog: Fulbright Scholars and Raphael re-enactment</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:37:31 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news4/</guid>
      <description>The AUS blog has had a facelift, with a new look, and new focus on telling the stories of AUS staff, faculty and students. We invite you to bookmark the blog so you can stay up-to-date on what is happening on and off campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUS high-flier: Cancer researcher making headlines</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:37:27 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Ghaleb Husseini, Associate Dean of Graduate Affairs and Research in the AUS College of Engineering, has been named one of 20 outstanding professors and researchers granted a 10-year UAE residency visa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: AUS sets itself ambitious research agenda</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:36:44 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As featured in a recent edition of Nature, AUS is advancing its research goals, with the university aspiring to be the region’s leading research university within five years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome from the Chancellor</title>
      <link>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:13:45 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://news.aus.edu/201902/news1/</guid>
      <description>The warmest greetings from American University of Sharjah, and welcome to STIR, the first edition of what will become the university’s quarterly newsletter.
It is an exciting time to be living in the UAE, and a very exciting time to be part of the AUS community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>